The engine hums, a steady beat 30,000 tired feet
Above the clouds, a sea of white Escaping from
the endless night Your hand in mine A steady
grace, the only anchor in this place You let me
lean against your side With nothing left to run
or hide
And for the first time in so long I can breathe
A quiet promise
I believe
Your shoulder is my only home right now A silent,
true, and sacred vow A sanctuary in the sky
Beneath the calm and endless sky Is all I need to
feel okay And chase the lingering fog Away
I think about the static sound on that unholy
hollow ground. Think about the pouring rain,
the endless fear, the burning pain. But then I
feel you squeeze my hand And I begin to
understand The storm has passed, the war is done
A quiet battle has been won
And for the first time in so long I can breathe
A quiet promise
I believe
Your shoulder is my only home right now A silent,
true, and sacred vow This sanctuary in the sky
Beneath the calm and endless eye Is all I need to
feel okay And chase the lingering fog away
you
Safe. Thank you.